{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868730012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868730012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868739711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868739711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868753237","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868753237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_aka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868766164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868766164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_iwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868776913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868776912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_ku"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868787461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868787461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868799743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868799743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868810273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868810273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ale"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868817053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868817053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ale"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868825678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868825678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_pe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868834291","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868834291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868843745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868843742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 327e3b70-9dc1-40a8-83e7-22d63fd0ee0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868859382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868859382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868868674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868868673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868878136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868878136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868884549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868884549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868890696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868890696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-11"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868896003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868896003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_13-4-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868902648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868902647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868910553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868910552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868915808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868915807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868921756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868921755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868927817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868927817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868934331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868934330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" e05ba888-dcb0-4e21-8ede-913115089e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_9-10-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868972146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868972146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__keno"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868982588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868982588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eusi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549868994038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549868994038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__oma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869003847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869003847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ogo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869014318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869014318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869027233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869027233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__mri"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869037503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869037503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__embe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869046471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869046471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__embe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869056860","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869056860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869068089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869068089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869083235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869083235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__enge"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869092329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869092329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write__enge"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869099320","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869099320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 1e3df8db-6984-4064-9995-561939479990"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__enge"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869111793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869111793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869118640","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869118640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869120207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869120207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwengine"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869124703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869124703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwengine"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869126284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869126283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869130136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869130135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869131746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869131746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alifuata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869136474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869136474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alifuata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869138071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869138071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alitumia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMIA"," userResponse":" ALITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869142842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869142842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alitumia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869144461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869144461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MWEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869148271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869148271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869149879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869149878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karatasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869154686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869154686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karatasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869156259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869156259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakaishi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAISHI"," userResponse":" WAKAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869160412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869160412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakaishi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869161997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869161997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alimpiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" ALIMPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869166247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869166247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alimpiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869167823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869167823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869172414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869172414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869174437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869174436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869174600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869174600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869181259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869181258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869192414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869192414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869198060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869198060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d2806f68-d519-4d2b-9c8a-b130b2e317f8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869211100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869211100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869217985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869217985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869219363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869219362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869220565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869220565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869221227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869221227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869228599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869228599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869230194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869230194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869231598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869231598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869233658","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869233658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869236487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869236486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869242314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869242313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869243950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869243950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869245587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869245587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869246072","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869246072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ukulima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869251352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869251352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869253457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869253457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869254694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869254693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869255500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869255499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869260719","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869260719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869262575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869262575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869263919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869263919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869265963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869265963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869273090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869273090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869274461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869274460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869276466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869276466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869277470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869277470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869278231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869278231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869285958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869285958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869286983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869286983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869293554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869293554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869296189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869296189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869302877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869302877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869304205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869304205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869305144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869305144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869310553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869310553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869311364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869311363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869317558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869317558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869318362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869318362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869318790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869318789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869324425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869324425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869325682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869325682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869331871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869331871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869333183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869333183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869333984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869333984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869339936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869339936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869341085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869341085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869341889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869341889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869347536","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869347536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869348383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869348383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869350233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869350232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869359911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869359911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" b93a2356-809d-4fc9-a2a0-26c87b0afd5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869379971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869379971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" alicheza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869389892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869389892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_blanketi_kitambaa-blanketi-walihisi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" blanketi"," userResponse":" blanketi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869405389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869405389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusubiri"," userResponse":" kusubiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869411410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869411409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nonkungu_nonkungu-hakuwahi-alikataa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nonkungu"," userResponse":" nonkungu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869417265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869417265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimwona_alimwona-mlangoni-kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimwona"," userResponse":" alimwona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869422644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869422643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusafiri_mwanangu-kusafiri-alisikia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusafiri"," userResponse":" alisikia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869431087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869431087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusafiri_mwanangu-kusafiri-alisikia"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusafiri"," userResponse":" kusafiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869436807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869436807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alishika_chunguni-pilipili-alishika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alishika"," userResponse":" chunguni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869448314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869448313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alishika_chunguni-pilipili-alishika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alishika"," userResponse":" pilipili"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869455027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869455027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alishika_chunguni-pilipili-alishika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alishika"," userResponse":" alishika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869466844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869466844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninaweza"," userResponse":" ninaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869473620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869473620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" tabasamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869480080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869480080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_samahani_nitakufa-mbinguni-samahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" samahani"," userResponse":" samahani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869485840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869485840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_samahani_nitakufa-mbinguni-samahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869491230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869491229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 62e6d340-609c-452e-b13b-3c48501e9790"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_samahani_nitakufa-mbinguni-samahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869505419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869505418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusafiri_mwanangu-kusafiri-alisikia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusafiri"," userResponse":" kusafiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869510340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869510340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" kumfanya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869517015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869517015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" tabasamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869532892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869532892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimwona_alimwona-mlangoni-kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimwona"," userResponse":" alimwona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869540110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869540110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" waliimba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869646817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869646817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" mwekundu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869658290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869658290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" alicheza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869664063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869664062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alishika_chunguni-pilipili-alishika"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alishika"," userResponse":" alishika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869669902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869669901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninaweza"," userResponse":" shambani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869676716","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869676716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninaweza"," userResponse":" hakuwahi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869683362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869683360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninaweza"," userResponse":" ninaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869688715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869688714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusubiri"," userResponse":" kitunguu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869828496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869828495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869905374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869905373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 2e0a682f-21fb-4e43-8647-0d83af1f8acf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549869952140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549869952140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 9bb9ccc8-c863-4a9b-8e5d-77367f221dc1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" mwekundu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870066711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870066711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 9bb9ccc8-c863-4a9b-8e5d-77367f221dc1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870074866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870074865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870075089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870075089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870076053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870076053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870077326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870077326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870080191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870080190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870081036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870081036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870081349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870081349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870082582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870082582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870086073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870086073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870087056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870087056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870087310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870087310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870088253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870088253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870091092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870091092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870092125","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870092125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870092599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870092599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870097124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870097124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870097214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870097214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 366dcdb5-9525-44a0-ba76-3baff8f19ce6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870120901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870120900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_blanketi_kitambaa-blanketi-walihisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" blanketi"," userResponse":" walihisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870179697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870179697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_blanketi_kitambaa-blanketi-walihisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" blanketi"," userResponse":" blanketi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870187749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870187749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusafiri_mwanangu-kusafiri-alisikia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusafiri"," userResponse":" kusafiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870215362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870215362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nonkungu_nonkungu-hakuwahi-alikataa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nonkungu"," userResponse":" nonkungu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870238866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870238866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" tabasamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870248506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870248506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimwona_alimwona-mlangoni-kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimwona"," userResponse":" alimwona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870315698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870315698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninaweza"," userResponse":" ninaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870362428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870362428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alishika_chunguni-pilipili-alishika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alishika"," userResponse":" alishika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870367817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870367817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_samahani_nitakufa-mbinguni-samahani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" samahani"," userResponse":" nitakufa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870388348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870388348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_samahani_nitakufa-mbinguni-samahani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" samahani"," userResponse":" samahani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870405388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870405388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" alicheza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870412271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870412271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusubiri"," userResponse":" kitunguu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870431122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870431122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusubiri"," userResponse":" kitunguu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870499328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870499328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusubiri"," userResponse":" polepole"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870507134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870507134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870540448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870540447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 857e2bb1-2f4e-4b49-b583-c2b168d9abb3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870552986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870552986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870560451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870560451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870561877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870561877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870565584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870565583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870567700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870567699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870569691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870569691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870569865","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870569865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870570189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870570189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870571333","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870571333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870572058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870572058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870573579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870573578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870573864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870573863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" 95142dac-2b31-46a1-92d9-6d1336eb5495"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870584674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870584674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870584897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870584897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870585859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870585859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870587131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870587131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870590030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870590030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870590874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870590874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870591188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870591188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870592423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870592422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870595936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870595935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870596921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870596921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870597174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870597174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870598118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870598118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870600956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870600956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870601991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870601991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870602469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870602468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870607003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870607003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549870607113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549870607113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_100450"," gameId":" d8591ed2-e0bd-46b8-b541-577496e89b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}